Wauregan and Quinebaug Company Records 1981.0010
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series VI: Labor Records, 1855-1958
  - Subseries C: Personnel Files, 1936-1958
    - Gagnon, Joseph A., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2548)
    - Gagnon, Joseph J., Jr., 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2549)
    - Gagnon, Leon, 1938 (Box 216, Folder 2550)
    - Gagnon, Mary P., 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2551)
    - Gagnon, Paul J., 1955 (Box 216, Folder 2552)
    - Gagnon, Rita Courtois, 1957 (Box 216, Folder 2553)
    - Galanos, George, 1944 (Box 216, Folder 2554)
    - Galanos, Harry, 1944 (Box 216, Folder 2555)
    - Galanos, Julia, 1945 (Box 216, Folder 2556)
    - Galanos, Katherine Mary, 1945 (Box 216, Folder 2557)
    - Gallichant, Joseph, 1943 (Box 216, Folder 2558)
    - Gallichant, Maurice, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2559)
    - Gallow, Beatrice, 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2560)
    - Galloway, John Larry, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2561)
    - Galloway, Lillian, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2562)
    - Galuski, Grace H., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2563)
    - Galuski, John J., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2564)
    - Galuski, William P., 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2565)
    - Gamache, Alfred, 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2566)
    - Gamache, Eva M., 1954 (Box 216, Folder 2567)
    - Gamache, Evelyn C., 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2568)
    - Gamache, Loretta Baril, 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2569)
    - Gamache, Mary Hayden, 1972 (Box 216, Folder 2570)
    - Gamache, Uldric, 1950 (Box 216, Folder 2571)
    - Gamelin, Joseph E., 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2572)
    - Gancarz, Germaine Marie Brodeur, 1957 (Box 216, Folder 2573)
    - Ganges, Mary O., 1943 (Box 216, Folder 2574)
    - Gangers, Michael, 1946 (Box 216, Folder 2575)
    - Gancarz, Peter E. (Ganges), 1953 (Box 216, Folder 2576)
    - Garabedian, Paul, 1954 (Box 216, Folder 2577)
    - Gardiner, Byron A., 1955 (Box 216, Folder 2578)
    - Gardiner, Richard B., 1938 (Box 216, Folder 2579)
    - Gardiner, Robert J., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2580)
    - Gardner, Earl T., 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2581)
    - Gareau, Paul, 1957 (Box 216, Folder 2582)
    - Gargano, Helen B., 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2583)
    - Gariepy, Adelard, 1950 (Box 216, Folder 2584)
    - Gariepy, Albert Alfred, 1944 (Box 216, Folder 2585)
    - Gariepy, Louise, 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2586)
    - Garneau, Alfred J., 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2587)
    - Garneau, Eva, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2589)
    - Garnier, Alexander J., 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2590)
    - Garnier, Alphonse H., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2591)
    - Garnier, Edmond A., 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2592)
    - Garnier, Edmond J., 1946 (Box 216, Folder 2593)
    - Garnier, Jeannette A., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2594)
    - Garnier, Irene, 1953 (Box 216, Folder 2595)
    - Garnier, Rosealda M. R., 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2596)
    - Garnier, Leona T., 1947 (Box 216, Folder 2597)
    - Garrett, Dwight L., 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2598)
    - Garstka, Bertha V., 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2599)
    - Garstka, Cecilia M., 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2600)
    - Garstka, Leonard J., 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2601)
    - Garstka, Stella E., 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2602)
    - Gasiorek, Mary W., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2603)
    - Gates, Denton H., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2604)
    - Gaudette, Arthur E., 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2605)
    - Gaudette, Clarence H., 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2606)
    - Gaudette, Margaret, 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2607)
    - Gaudreau, Alexina, 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2608)
    - Gaudreau, Amede L., 1957 (Box 216, Folder 2609)
    - Gaudreau, Antonio J., 1949 (Box 216, Folder 2610)
    - Gaudreau, Arthur, 1955 (Box 216, Folder 2611)
    - Gaudreau, Augustine, 1955 (Box 216, Folder 2612)
    - Gaudreau, Aurore V., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2613)
    - Gaudreau, Elizabeth G., 1949 (Box 216, Folder 2614)
    - Gaudreau, Emile, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2615)
    - Gaudreau, Eugene, 1953 (Box 216, Folder 2616)
    - Gaudreau, Francis O., 1946 (Box 216, Folder 2617)
    - Gaudreau, Jennie S., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2618)
    - Gaudreau, Leona, 1945 (Box 216, Folder 2619)
    - Gaudreau, Lorina, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2620)
    - Gaudreau, Lucille F., 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2621)
    - Gaudreau, Margaret, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2622)
    - Gaudreau, Mary B., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2623)
    - Gaudreau, Norman, 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2624)
    - Gaudreau, Omer A., 1954 (Box 216, Folder 2625)
    - Gaudreau, Roland R., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2626)
    - Gauthier, Adolph, 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2627)
    - Gauthier, Alfred N., Jr., 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2628)
    - Gauthier, Ella A. P., 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2629)
    - Gauthier, Eugene, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2630)
    - Gauthier, Eugene Albert, 1951 (Box 216, Folder 2631)
    - Gauthier, Eva L., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2632)
    - Gauthier, James E., 1943 (Box 216, Folder 2633)
    - Gauthier, Leontine, 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2634)
    - Gauthier, Romeo R., 1938 (Box 216, Folder 2635)
    - Gauthier, Ronald, 19 (Box 216, Folder 2636)
    - Gauthier, Rose, 1954 (Box 216, Folder 2637)
    - Gauthier, Simone, 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2638)
    - Gauthier, Wilfred J., 1953 (Box 216, Folder 2639)
    - Gauthier, William, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2640)
    - Gauthier, William, Jr., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2641)
    - Gauvin, Claire, 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2642)
    - Gawlik, Joseph J., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2643)
    - Gay, Mary, 1943 (Box 216, Folder 2644)
    - Gazeau, Regina T., 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2645)
    - Gazette, Henry G., Jr. (George Henry), 1950 (Box 216, Folder 2646)
    - Gazette, Rita, 1957 (Box 216, Folder 2647)
    - Gebo, Fred J., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2648)
    - Geherean, Charles F., 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2649)
    - Geherean, Lillie, 1944 (Box 216, Folder 2650)
    - Gelinas, Adrien E., 1947 (Box 216, Folder 2651)
    - Gelinas, Blanche, 1949 (Box 216, Folder 2652)
    - Gelinas, Ephraim, 1938 (Box 216, Folder 2653)
    - Gelinas, Maxime, 19 (Box 216, Folder 2654)
    - Gendreau, Almoza R., 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2655)
    - Gendreau, Donat, 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2656)
    - Gendreau, Herve, 1954 (Box 216, Folder 2657)
    - Gendreau, Joachim J., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2658)
    - Gendreau, Rene D., 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2659)
    - Generous, Richard, 1949 (Box 216, Folder 2660)
    - Genest, Donald, 1946 (Box 216, Folder 2661)
    - Genest, Theresa Mary, 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2662)
    - Gerard, Frank, 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2663)
    - Gercic, Christy, 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2664)
    - Gercich, Anna P., 1957 (Box 216, Folder 2665)
    - Germain, Emile J., 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2666)
    - Gero, Joseph, 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2667)
    - Gero, Ray, 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2668)
    - Gervais, Arsena F., 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2669)
    - Gervais, Normand F., 1954 (Box 216, Folder 2670)
    - Gervais, Erest J., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2671)
    - Gervais, Leo, 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2672)
    - Gesualdo, Mary T., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2673)
    - Giambattista, Madeline G., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2674)
    - Giard, Adelard, 1957 (Box 217, Folder 2675)
    - Gibeault, Alfred J., 1954 (Box 217, Folder 2676)
    - Gibeault, Alphonse C., 1952 (Box 217, Folder 2677)
    - Gibeault, Dora T. C., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2678)
    - Gibeault, Eugene A., 1957 (Box 217, Folder 2679)
    - Gibeault, Joseph N., 1954 (Box 217, Folder 2680)
    - Gibeault, Louis J., 1938 (Box 217, Folder 2681)
    - Gibeault, Margaret, 1946 (Box 217, Folder 2682)
    - Gibeault, Norman V., 1947 (Box 217, Folder 2683)
    - Gibeault, Odinas M., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2684)
    - Gibeault, Stella M. M., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2685)
    - Gibson, Leo F., 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2686)
    - Giermata, Frank J., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2687)
    - Giguere, Albert, 1952 (Box 217, Folder 2688)
    - Giguere, Bernice Jane, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2689)
    - Giguere, Irene, 1944 (Box 217, Folder 2690)
    - Giguere, John Joseph, 1950 (Box 217, Folder 2691)
    - Giguere, Paul, 1943 (Box 217, Folder 2692)
    - Gilbert, Emma M., 1940 (Box 217, Folder 2693)
    - Gilbert, Gladys, 1943 (Box 217, Folder 2694)
    - Gilbert, Lucille, 1954 (Box 217, Folder 2695)
    - Gilbert, Rita Doris, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2696)
    - Gilbert, Rose A. B., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2697)
    - Gilbert, Theresa, 1949 (Box 217, Folder 2698)
    - Gilbert, Thomas F., 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2699)
    - Gileau, Zepherie H., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2700)
    - Giles, Julye Hardell, 1945 (Box 217, Folder 2701)
    - Gingras, Adelard J., 1952 (Box 217, Folder 2702)
    - Gingras, Frances S., 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2703)
    - Gingras, Joseph F., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2704)
    - Gingras, Leon J., 1950 (Box 217, Folder 2705)
    - Gingras, Norman, 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2706)
    - Gill, John A., 1943 (Box 217, Folder 2707)
    - Girard, Florence M., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2708)
    - Girard, Roland J., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2709)
    - Girardin, Willie E., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2710)
    - Gistedt, Carl O., 1952 (Box 217, Folder 2711)
    - Gladu, Edmond V., 1945 (Box 217, Folder 2712)
    - Gladu, Emma P., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2713)
    - Gladue, Frank J., 1942 (Box 217, Folder 2714)
    - Glaude, Aurore B., 1946 (Box 217, Folder 2715)
    - Glaude, Claire R., 1946 (Box 217, Folder 2716)
    - Glaude, Joseph A., 1938 (Box 217, Folder 2717)
    - Glaude, Mary, 1954 (Box 217, Folder 2718)
    - Gmyr, Mary Z. C., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2719)
    - Gobeille, Marie L. A., 1940 (Box 217, Folder 2720)
    - Godaire, Lorraine, 1955 (Box 217, Folder 2721)
    - Godaire, Mary, 1948 (Box 217, Folder 2722)
    - Godak, Peter, 1942 (Box 217, Folder 2723)
    - Godchild, Edith C., 1942 (Box 217, Folder 2724)
    - Goddard, John Howard (Howard J.), 1945 (Box 217, Folder 2725)
    - Godere, Wilfred, 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2726)
    - Goderre, Claire R., 1940 (Box 217, Folder 2727)
    - Golas, Catherine K., 1938 (Box 217, Folder 2728)
    - Golas, Clara J., 1952 (Box 217, Folder 2729)
    - Golash, Albert F., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2730)
    - Golasz, Frances, 1944 (Box 217, Folder 2731)
    - Gomes, Antonio S., 1942 (Box 217, Folder 2732)
    - Gomes, John, 1955 (Box 217, Folder 2733)
    - Goodridge, George, Jr., 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2734)
    - Gordon, Henry, 1940 (Box 217, Folder 2735)
    - Gordon, Lawrence C., 1940 (Box 217, Folder 2736)
    - Gorman, Thomas A., 1951 (Box 217, Folder 2737)
    - Gorski, Estelle D., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2738)
    - Gosselin, Hector R., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2739)
    - Gosselin, Jules, 1944 (Box 217, Folder 2740)
    - Gosselin, Napoleon W. T., 1944 (Box 217, Folder 2741)
    - Gosselin, Roger A., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2742)
    - Gosselin, Rose B., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2743)
    - Gosselin, Roseline E. H., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2744)
    - Gould, Archie J., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2745)
    - Gould, Helen, 1942 (Box 217, Folder 2746)
    - Gould, Lucia C., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2747)
    - Goulet, Annie L., 1954 (Box 217, Folder 2748)
    - Goulet, Bernice I., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2749)
    - Goulet, Blanche R., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2750)
    - Goulet, Mary, 1943 (Box 217, Folder 2751)
    - Goulet, Morris P., 1940 (Box 217, Folder 2752)
    - Gouseski, Stella G., 1942 (Box 217, Folder 2753)
    - Goven, Arthur J., Jr., 1951 (Box 217, Folder 2754)
    - Goven, Arthur J., Sr., 1949 (Box 217, Folder 2755)
    - Goven, Earl Joseph, 1946 (Box 217, Folder 2756)
    - Goven, Emily Lena, 1950 (Box 217, Folder 2757)
    - Goven, John E., 1950 (Box 217, Folder 2758)
    - Goven, John T., 1943 (Box 217, Folder 2759)
    - Goven, Lucille M., 1954 (Box 217, Folder 2760)
    - Goven, Martha C. B., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2761)
    - Goyette, Elphege, 1950 (Box 217, Folder 2762)
    - Grable, Norman, Jr., 1952 (Box 217, Folder 2763)
    - Grabowski, Mary P., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2764)
    - Grandalski, Frank, 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2765)
    - Grassl, Joseph, 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2766)
    - Gravel, Doris, 1955 (Box 217, Folder 2767)
    - Gravelin, Fred L., 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2768)
    - Gaveline, Joseph L., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2769)
    - Green, JOhn N., 1940 (Box 217, Folder 2770)
    - Greene, Clifford I., 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2771)
    - Greene, Everett D., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2772)
    - Greene, Helen Goulet, 1949 (Box 217, Folder 2773)
    - Greene, Kenneth B., 1950 (Box 217, Folder 2774)
    - Greenhalgh, Agnes N., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2775)
    - Gregoire, Bernard, 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2776)
    - Grenier, Beatrice, 1955 (Box 217, Folder 2777)
    - Greniere, Georgette R., 1943 (Box 217, Folder 2778)
    - Grenier, Laura, 1942 (Box 217, Folder 2779)
    - Grenier, Lois T., 1943 (Box 217, Folder 2780)
    - Grenier, Marie Doris, 1945 (Box 217, Folder 2781)
    - Grenier, Rose A., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2782)
    - Grenon, Antoinette Fournier, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2783)
    - Grenon, Elizabeth, 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2784)
    - Grenon, Norman, 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2785)
    - Grezesiak, Czeslawa R., 1947 (Box 217, Folder 2786)
    - Griggs, Barbara, 1955 (Box 217, Folder 2787)
    - Grimshaw, Josephine P., 1947 (Box 217, Folder 2788)
    - Grimshaw, Frances, 1947 (Box 217, Folder 2789)
    - Grimshaw, Michael E., 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2790)
    - Grise, Jean, 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2791)
    - Grise, Norman D., 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2792)
    - Grobofski, Sophie, 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2793)
    - Gruszka, Jawina, 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2794)
    - Gruszka, Stanley, 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2795)
    - Grzysiewicz, Philip, 1955 (Box 217, Folder 2796)
    - Guertin, Arthur, 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2797)
    - Guertin, Frank X., 1955 (Box 217, Folder 2798)
    - Guertin, Ovila J., 1952 (Box 217, Folder 2799)
    - Guertin, Prudent E., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2800)
    - Guertin, Valmore, 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2801)
    - Guilbault, Hildige, 1948 (Box 217, Folder 2802)
    - Guilbault, Joseph Alphonse, 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2803)
    - Guillotte, Allan (Allen), 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2804)
    - Guillemette, Eugene L., 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2805)
    - Guillemette, George C., 1938 (Box 217, Folder 2807)
    - Guillemette, Jennie P., 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2808)
    - Guillemette, Lionel S., 1951 (Box 217, Folder 2809)
    - Guillemette, Rita, 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2810)
    - Guillemette, Theodore M., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2811)
    - Guillemette, Wilfred H., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2812)
    - Guillemette, Yvonne M. A. Beauregard, 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2813)
    - Guimont, Arsene, 1942 (Box 217, Folder 2814)
    - Guimont, Camille L., 1944 (Box 217, Folder 2815)
    - Guimont, Emelda A., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2816)
    - Guimont, Emile E., 1938 (Box 217, Folder 2817)
    - Guimont, Marie A. F., 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2818)
    - Guimont, Ovide, 1937 (Box 217, Folder 2819)
    - Guimont, Viateur, 1944 (Box 217, Folder 2820)
    - Guinard, Harry J., 1948 (Box 217, Folder 2821)
    - Guldenberg, Clara, 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2822)
    - Gunther, Madelyne J. Hardell, 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2823)
    - Gursky, Stanley, 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2824)
    - Hagberg, Arlene (Hagburg), 1951 (Box 217, Folder 2825)
    - Hall, Grace, 1954 (Box 217, Folder 2826)
    - Hall, Jean E., 1947 (Box 217, Folder 2827)
    - Hamel, Charles, 1955 (Box 217, Folder 2828)
    - Hamel, Louis A., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2829)
    - Hamel, Marguerite, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2830)
    - Hamel, Marie A. C., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2831)
    - Hamel, Mary G., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2838)
    - Hamelin, Edward, 1957 (Box 217, Folder 2833)
    - Hamlin, Fred, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2834)
    - Harbour, Leo A., 1938 (Box 217, Folder 2835)
    - Harbour, Omer E., 1938 (Box 217, Folder 2836)
    - Harbour, Rose R., 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2837)
    - Hardell, John M., Jr., 1942 (Box 217, Folder 2838)
    - Hardell, Sophie, 1943 (Box 217, Folder 2839)
    - Harney, James, 1957 (Box 217, Folder 2840)
    - Harralle, William, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2841)
    - Harrell, Beatrice L., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2842)
    - Harrington, Bertha M. B., 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2843)
    - Harrington, Ruth, 1946 (Box 217, Folder 2844)
    - Harris, George E., Jr., 1952 (Box 217, Folder 2845)
    - Hart, Adelard, 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2846)
    - Hart, Elmer, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2847)
    - Hart, Wilfred Joseph, 1947 (Box 217, Folder 2848)
    - Haskell, Arthur A., 1948 (Box 217, Folder 2849)
    - Haskell, Donald B., 1945 (Box 217, Folder 2850)
    - Hassila, John, 1945 (Box 217, Folder 2851)
    - Hastings, Mertis, 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2852)
    - Hauser, Herman N., 1948 (Box 217, Folder 2853)
    - Hauser, Irene S., 1942 (Box 217, Folder 2854)
    - Hauser, Robert, 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2855)
    - Hauserman, Jeannette, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 2856)
    - Havel, George A., 1952 (Box 217, Folder 2857)
    - Hawes, Blanche, 1956 (Box 217, Folder 2858)
    - Hawkins, Herbert C., 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2859)
    - Hawkins, Irwin H., 1951 (Box 217, Folder 2860)
    - Hawkins, Theresa Deloge, 1953 (Box 217, Folder 2861)
    - Hayhurst, John, 1946 (Box 217, Folder 2862)
    - Hayston, Delia G., 1938 (Box 217, Folder 2963)
    - Hayston, Frederick, 1939 (Box 217, Folder 2864)
    - Heath, Frank Edward, 1953 (Box 218, Folder 2865)
    - Hebert, Agnes N., 1954 (Box 218, Folder 2866)
    - Hebert, Annie A. H., 1949 (Box 218, Folder 2867)
    - Hebert, Arthur, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2868)
    - Hebert, Donalda, 1948 (Box 218, Folder 2869)
    - Hebert, Helena B., 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2870)
    - Hebert, Irene B. J., 1956 (Box 218, Folder 2871)
    - Hebert, Napoleon J., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2872)
    - Hebert, Philip, 1939 (Box 218, Folder 1873)
    - Hebert, Roy N., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2874)
    - Hebert, Yvonne M., 19 (Box 218, Folder 2875)
    - Helbig, Herbert E., 1950 (Box 218, Folder 2876)
    - Helbig, Lenore F., 1946 (Box 218, Folder 2877)
    - Helie, Alcide, 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2878)
    - Helie, Eugenie B., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2879)
    - Helie, Joseph A., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2880)
    - Helie, Paul A., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2881)
    - Helper, Alexander, 1938 (Box 218, Folder 2882)
    - Helstrom, Harry F., 1943 (Box 218, Folder 2883)
    - Helstrom, Jennie H. Wernicki, 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2884)
    - Henderson, Blanche M., 1947 (Box 218, Folder 2885)
    - Henderson, Edward W., 1938 (Box 218, Folder 2886)
    - Henderson, Eva M., 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2887)
    - Henderson, Raymond, 1947 (Box 218, Folder 2888)
    - Henderson, Raymond, 1946 (Box 218, Folder 2889)
    - Henderson, Rita, 1951 (Box 218, Folder 2890)
    - Hentschel, Harold J., 1939 (Box 218, Folder 2891)
    - Heon, Denise Martel, 1953 (Box 218, Folder 2892)
    - Heon, Emile D., 1952 (Box 218, Folder 2893)
    - Herard, Albert J., 1952 (Box 218, Folder 2894)
    - Herard, Dorothy G., 1939 (Box 218, Folder 2895)
    - Herard, Eliza, 1952 (Box 218, Folder 2896)
    - Herard, Emile J., 1944 (Box 218, Folder 2897)
    - Herard, Raymond, 1957 (Box 218, Folder 2898)
    - Herbert, Marion I., 1940 (Box 218, Folder 2899)
    - Herkel, Alton E., 1940 (Box 218, Folder 2900)
    - Heroux, Emile A., 1955 (Box 218, Folder 2901)
    - Herrick, Herbert, 1945 (Box 218, Folder 2902)
    - Hetherson, Richard J., 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2903)
    - Hewitt, Diana, 1954 (Box 218, Folder 2904)
    - Hewitt, Frank, 1955 (Box 218, Folder 2905)
    - Hewko, Joseph, 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2906)
    - Hewko, Wasyl, 1952 (Box 218, Folder 2907)
    - Hicks, Salodius Z., Jr., 1951 (Box 218, Folder 2908)
    - Hill, Bertha Hazel, 1943 (Box 218, Folder 2909)
    - Hinds, Eleanor M., 1957 (Box 218, Folder 2910)
    - Hilton, Asa, Jr., 1939 (Box 218, Folder 2911)
    - Hipnar, Joseph, 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2912)
    - Hirst, Clara F., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2913)
    - Hirst, Frank F., 1941 (Box 218, Folder 2914)
    - Hirst, Walter G., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2915)
    - Hitt, Frederick A., 1941 (Box 218, Folder 2916)
    - Hitt, Melanise F., 1940 (Box 218, Folder 2917)
    - Holbert, Gloria, 1956 (Box 218, Folder 2918)
    - Holgerson, Gladys B., 1954 (Box 218, Folder 2919)
    - Holmes, Verda B. C., 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2920)
    - Holt, Earl S., 1952 (Box 218, Folder 2621)
    - Holt, Lena, 1952 (Box 218, Folder 2922)
    - Holt, Raymond, 1954 (Box 218, Folder 2923)
    - Hopkins, Doris C., 1939 (Box 218, Folder 2924)
    - Hopkins, Franklin R., 1954 (Box 218, Folder 2925)
    - Hopkins, Frederick S., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2926)
    - Hopkins, Justine, 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2927)
    - Hopkins, Sidney G., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2928)
    - Hopkins, William, 1947 (Box 218, Folder 2929)
    - Houghton, Cecile, 1955 (Box 218, Folder 2930)
    - Houle, Azarias, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 2931)
    - Houle, James, 1948 (Box 218, Folder 2932)
    - Houle, Joseph A., 1954 (Box 218, Folder 2933)
    - Houle, Louisa L., 1957 (Box 218, Folder 2934)
    - Houle, Lucinda, 1939 (Box 218, Folder 2935)
    - House, Bertha E., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2936)
    - House, Evelyn, 1945 (Box 218, Folder 2937)
    - House, Herbert, 1955 (Box 218, Folder 2938)
    - Howard, Henry S., 1941 (Box 218, Folder 2939)
    - Howard, Irving J., 1939 (Box 218, Folder 2940)
    - Howarth, Charles H., 1938 (Box 218, Folder 2941)
    - Howcroft, John, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 2942)
    - Howell, Ray, 1947 (Box 218, Folder 2943)
    - Howland, Ellis King, Jr., 1948 (Box 218, Folder 2944)
    - Hubbard, Elwood, 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2945)
    - Hubert, Anatole, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 2946)
    - Hubert, Beatrice D., 1941 (Box 218, Folder 2947)
    - Hubert, Emil V., 1957 (Box 218, Folder 2948)
    - Hubert, Lawrence, 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2949)
    - Hubert, Loretta B., 1947 (Box 218, Folder 2950)
    - Hubert, Lorraine B., 1947 (Box 218, Folder 2951)
    - Hubert, Lumina, 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2952)
    - Hubert, Omer C., 1952 (Box 218, Folder 2953)
    - Hubert, Roland, 1956 (Box 218, Folder 2954)
    - Hubert, Rosario, 1956 (Box 218, Folder 2955)
    - Hubert, Yvonne, 1951 (Box 218, Folder 2956)
    - Humes, Melvin R., 1952 (Box 218, Folder 2957)
    - Humes, Theresa, 1956 (Box 218, Folder 2958)
    - Humes, Walter, 1950 (Box 218, Folder 2959)
    - Hunter, Judson, 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2960)
    - Huntington, Alma F., 1940 (Box 218, Folder 2961)
    - Hurlbutt, Norma, 1945 (Box 218, Folder 2962)
    - Hutchins, William L., 1955 (Box 218, Folder 2963)
    - Hutchinson, Beatrice B., 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2964)
    - Ide, Dolores C., 1955 (Box 218, Folder 2965)
    - Ide, Elsie, 1950 (Box 218, Folder 2966)
    - Ide, James, 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2967)
    - Ingves, Rainer A., 1950 (Box 218, Folder 2968)
    - Inskip, Delbert H., 1946 (Box 218, Folder 2969)
    - Izbicki, John A., 1939 (Box 218, Folder 2970)
    - Jackson, James, 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2971)
    - Jacques, Irving, Jr., 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2972)
    - Jacques, Irving Linwood, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 2973)
    - Jacques, Julian H., 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2974)
    - Jacques, Olive B., 1951 (Box 218, Folder 2975)
    - Jaffre, Arthur J., 1952 (Box 218, Folder 2976)
    - Jakus, Stanley, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 2977)
    - Janiszewski, Kasimiera, 1955 (Box 218, Folder 2978)
    - Janowski, Paulina K., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2979)
    - Jarusz, Peter, 1942 (Box 218, Folder 2980)
    - Jarvais, Aldor J., 1956 (Box 218, Folder 2981)
    - Jelbert, Ida C., 1937 (Box 218, Folder 2982)
    - Jendrewski, Rita, 1956 (Box 218, Folder 2983)
    - Jennings, Doris, 1951 (Box 218, Folder 2984)
    - Jernstrom, Alvin E., 1950 (Box 218, Folder 2985)
    - Jewell, Doris, 1956 (Box 218, Folder 2986)
    - Jodoin, Dona, 1952 (Box 218, Folder 2987)
    - Jodoin, Louis, 1946 (Box 218, Folder 2988)
    - Jodoin, Mae, 1954 (Box 218, Folder 2989)
    - Jodoin, William, 1955 (Box 218, Folder 2990)
    - JOhns, Nicholas E., 1948 (Box 218, Folder 2991)
    - Johnson, Alfreda, 1947 (Box 218, Folder 2992)
    - Johnson, Charles W., 1945 (Box 218, Folder 2993)
    - Johnson, Emil, 1957 (Box 218, Folder 2994)
    - Johnson, Marie E., 1951 (Box 218, Folder 2995)